

# Amir Hallaji

## Computer Engineer

Dreams come true...

## Summary

I am studying Computer Eingeering (Artificial Intelligence) for my master's degree at Shahid Beheshti University. I got my bachelor's degree in computer engineering at Shahid Beheshti University. About work and experience, I am currently working as a Junior Software Engineer (Backend Developer) at Snapp company. Snapp is the first and largest ride-hailing platform in the middle east. (Iranian Uber)

#### Education

2022–2024 **M.sc**, *Shahid Beheshti University*, Iran, Computer Engineering - Artificial Intelligence

2018–2022 **B.SC**, Shahid Beheshti University, Iran, GPA 18.00/20 Computer Engineering

2014–2018 **Diploma**, *Salam Tajrish High School*, Tehran, Iran, *GPA 19.95/20* Mathematics and Physics

## Work Experience

Jan 2022 - **Software Engineer (Golang)**, Snapp Inc, Tehran, Iran

now

2021 Programmer Internship, MavaraTech Company, Tehran, Iran

2019 - now Programming Teacher, Salam Tajrish high school, Tehran, Iran

## Tools and Technologies

Golang Intermediate 2021 - Present
C, C++ Intermediate 2018 - Present

Python	Intermediate	2020 - Present
Docker	Intermediate	2022 - Present
React JS	Intermediate	2021 - Present
Javascript	Intermediate	2020 - Present
Java	Intermediate	2019 - Present
HTML,CSS	Intermediate	2019 - Present

## Course Projects

#### Linkedin Data Analysis and Job prediction

Machine Learning: Predicting people job based on educations, skills and experience

#### Topic news Classification

NLP: Predicting the news topic by NLP

#### Dog breeds Prediction:

Image Processing: predicting dog breeds among 120 breeds

#### Google Classroom

Android Google classroom Advanced Programming Course

#### Jetpack joyride

Jetpack joyride game: Introduction to Programming final project

## Teaching Experience

- 2019 Instructor, Introduction to Programming, Salam Tajrish high school, Tehran, Iran
  - 2020 Teacher Assistant, Machine Learning, Shahid Beheshti University, Tehran, Iran
  - 2020 Teacher Assistant, Discrete Mathematics, Shahid Beheshti University, Tehran, Iran
- 2019-2021 **Teacher Assistant**, Advanced Programming, Shahid Beheshti University, Tehran, Iran
  - 2020- Teacher Assistant, Specialized English, Shahid Beheshti University, Tehran, Iran

#### Related Courses

- O Bachelor Thesis: 19/20
- Internet Engineering: 20/20
- O Computational Intelligence: 19/20
- Software Engineering: 19/20
- O Algorithm Design: 19.05/20
- O Database Lab: 20/20
- O Advanced Programming: 16.1/20
- Introduction to Programming: 16/20
- O Data Structures and Algorithms: 16.6/20
- Operating Systems: 17.9/20
- O Computer Architecture: 17/20
- O System Analysis and Design: 20/20

- O Discrete Mathematics: 18/20
- O Engineering mathematics: 18.3/20

#### Honors & Awards

- 2017 Iran Language Institute, Finished Advanced Levels
- 2021 **Wikipedia Farsi**, wrote about Invasive Weed Optimization algorithm in Wikipedia Farsi

## Languages

- O Persian: Native
- O English: Professional working Proficiency

#### Interests

- Machine Learning, Deep Learning
- Image Processing
- Hacking and Security
- Internet of things